A Finding Aid to the Fischbach Gallery Records, 1937-2015, bulk 1963-1977, in the Archives of American Art AAA.fiscgall
Archives of American Art
- Artists and Exhibitions Files, 1937-1977; Series 1; (Boxes 1-18, 28; 18 linear feet)
  - Gorski, Daniel (Box 7)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Gottlieb, Adolf (Box 7)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Grosvenor, Robert (Box 7)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "Critical Reviews", 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1970; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 25-26)
    - Press Releases, circa 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Blueprints--List Water Piece, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Photos of Installations, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1966-1970; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 31-33)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, 1965-1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Haber, Ira Joel (Box 7)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1971 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Photos of Installations, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1969-1972; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 38-39)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Hartung, Hans (Box 8)
    - General Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1961 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Henry, Dale (Box 8)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970s (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hesse, Eva (Box 8)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970s (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1971; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1970; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Photos of Installations, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1970; (6 folders) (Box 8, Folder 20-25)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1967 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hokanson, Hans (Box 8)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1960s (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Sketches of Works of Art, circa 1964 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Insley, Will (Box 8)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1966-1975 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Insho, Domoto (Box 8)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1962 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1962 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Isham, Sheila (Box 8)
    - General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Jacquette, Yvonne (Box 9)
    - Biographical Information, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Lists of Works of Art, 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1965-1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1968-1976; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
    - Photos of Installations, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1967-1973; (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 8-10)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Jensen, Bill (Box 9)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Judd, Donald (Box 9)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Katz, Alex (Box 9)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1965 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Bienal de Arte Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Brusberg Gallery Corresopndence, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence, 1962-1971; (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 20-23)
    - "Katz Retrospective" Correspondence, 1970-1971; (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 24-26)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1971; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
    - Print Accounts Correspondence, circa 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1962-1971 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - "Alex Katz is Painting a Poet"--by Lucy Lippard, circa 1970 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1962-1971 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1962-1971; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1962-1971; (11 folders) (Box 10, Folder 3-13)
    - Press Releases, 1965-1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Photos of Installations, 1968-1971; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1957-1971; (3 folders) (Box 10, Folder 18-20)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1957-1971; (8 folders) (Box 11, Folder 1-8)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 11, Folder 9-11)
  - Kilstrom, Kenneth (Box 11)
    - Biographical Information, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Slides of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Krushenick, Nicholas (Box 11)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - General Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Photos and Slides of Works of Art, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Kuehn, Gary (Box 11)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1971 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1971 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1968 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Kuriloff, Aaron (Box 11)
    - Biographical Information, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Photos of Installations, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1963-1965; (3 folders) (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
    - Slides of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Larsen, Jack (Box 12)
    - Biographical Information, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence and Exhibition Information, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Photo and Slides of Works of Art, circa 1974; (Oversized Material Housed in Box 27, Oversized Photo of Work of Art) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lenk, Thomas (Box 12)
    - Biographical Information, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1971 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1971; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
    - Press Releases, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      (Oversized material housed in Box 28)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1965 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Levine, Les (Box 12)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - General Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - "Iris Print out Portrait" Correspondence, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1964-1971 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1972; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 26-28)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1972; (4 folders) (Box 12, Folder 29-32)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Interview, Brydon Smith--"Slipcover, A Place", 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Photos of Installations, 1966-1972; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1967-1972; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1967 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lists of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Longo, Vincent (Box 13)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - McCauley, Nancy (Box 13)
    - General Correspondence, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Photos and Slides of Works of Art, circa 1965 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Mangold, Robert (Box 13)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1964-1974; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Clippings, 1963-1974; (4 folders) (Box 13, Folder 21-24)
    - Press Releases, 1963-1971 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - "Robert Mangold and the Implications of Monochrome"--by Lucy Lippard, circa 1965 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1963-1968 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Photos of Installations, 1967-1972; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 28-29)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1972; (3 folders) (Box 13, Folder 30-32)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1969; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 33-34)
  - Mangold, Sylvia (Box 14)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lists of Works of Art, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Photos of Installations, 1969-1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1968-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Martin, Knox (Box 14)
    - Biographical Information, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - General Corresopndence, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, circa 1960s (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Photos of Installations, circa 1960s; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1962-1966; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Metcalf, James (Box 14)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1960 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Morris, Robert (Box 14)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1964-1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Neu, Renee (Box 14)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Neuberger, Babette (Box 14)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1950 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Ohlson, Doug (Box 14)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1969 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Gallery/Installation Floor Plans, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1964-1973 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1964-1973; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 30-31)
    - Press Releases, circa 1960s (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Photos of Installations, 1967-1969; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 34-35)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1964-1969; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 36-37)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Olivotto, Germano (Box 14)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Parker, Raymond (Box 14)
    - Biographical Information, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1968-1974 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1974 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Photos of Installations, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1969-1974; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Parsons, Betty (Box 15)
    - Photos of Installations, circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Photos and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Pavlos (Box 15)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1967 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Photos of Installations, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Pfahler, Georg Karl (Box 15)
    - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1965-1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965-1971; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Picard, Lil (Box 15)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert (Box 15)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Reino, Alejandro (Box 15)
    - General Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Ryan, Anne (Box 15)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1968 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Journal (Copy), 1938-1942 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - General Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1968 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1940-1953 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1950s (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Negatives and Slides of Works of Art, circa 1968 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Ryman, Robert (Box 15)
    - Biographical Information, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Guggenheim Correspondence, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Outside Exhibition Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1967-1974 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1967-1974; (2 folders; Oversized Material Housed in Box 28, Oversized Exhibition Catalog) (Box 15, Folder 40-41)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Photos of Installations, 1967-1969; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 43-44)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1961-1969 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1961-1969; (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s; (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 4-6)
  - Sanejouand, J.M. (Box 16)
    - Exhibition Catalog, circa 1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Schneeman, George (Box 16)
    - Photos of Installations, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Shostak, Ed (Box 16)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Simon, Sidney (Box 16)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Photos of Installations, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Slavin, Arlene (Box 16)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Slonem, Hunt (Box 16)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1971-1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Leon Polk (Box 16)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Tony (Box 16)
    - Biographical Information, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1971 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Photos of the Artist, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Photos of Construction of Works of Art, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Photos of Installations, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 26-27)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1961-1969; (4 folders) (Box 16, Folder 28-31)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 32-33)
  - Sonenberg, Jack (Box 16)
    - Biographical Information, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - General Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Exhibtion Announcement, circa 1974 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 37-38)
  - Stadler, Albert (Box 16)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Stefanelli, Joseph (Box 16)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1963 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - General Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1957-1962 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Steiner, Michael (Box 17)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - General Corresopndence, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Stella, Frank (Box 17)
    - Articles and Clippings, circa 1966 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Strick, Racelle (Box 17)
    - Biographical Information, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Sugarman, George (Box 17)
    - Biographical Information, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Lists of Works of Art Returned to Sugarman, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1969; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1960s (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Photos of Construction of Works of Art, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Photos of Installations, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1960-1969; (5 folders) (Box 17, Folder 20-24)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Sultan, Altoon (Box 17)
    - General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Swain, Robert (Box 17)
    - Biographical Information, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Photos of the Artist, cirac 1960s (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Photos of Installations, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1967-1969; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 36-37)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Tadasky (Box 17)
    - Biographical Information, 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1964-1969 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1964-1969 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Tinguely (Box 17)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Tisa, Ken (Box 17)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Tobey, Mark (Box 17)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Twombly, Cy (Box 17)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Uncini, Guisseppe (Box 17)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Viner, Frank Lincoln (Box 18)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Weinstein, Jeffrey S. (Box 18)
    - Biographical Information, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Widmier, Hank (Box 18)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Wurmfeld, Sanford (Box 18)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970s (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Artist's Copy of Correspondence, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Consignment and Loan Information, 1967, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Photos of the Artist, circa 1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Photos of Installations, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)